{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "大",
      "answer": "Dà | big, large"
    },
    {
      "question": "多少",
      "answer": "Duōshǎo | how many, how much"
    },
    {
      "question": "多",
      "answer": "Duō | many, much"
    },
    {
      "question": "少",
      "answer": "Shǎo | few, less"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜欢",
      "answer": "Xǐhuān | to like"
    },
    {
      "question": "外语",
      "answer": "Wàiyǔ | foreign language"
    },
    {
      "question": "外",
      "answer": "Wài | foreign, outside"
    },
    {
      "question": "语",
      "answer": "Yǔ | language"
    },
    {
      "question": "外国",
      "answer": "Wàiguó | foreign country"
    },
    {
      "question": "白",
      "answer": "Bái | hundred"
    }
  ]
}
